# HOANG KHAC



## **Online Resume**



#### www.hoangkn.com

I created it using React and Gatsby.

## **Contact**

#### **Address**

**Budapest**, Hungary

## Phone

+36 207783223

#### **Email**

hoangkn dev@icloud.com

# Languages

English, Hungarian

# **Summary**

I am an enthusiastic front-end developer with 4 years' experience including React, Angular, TypeScript, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, REST, Git. I have been experimenting with latest technologies recently including React, Gatsby, CSS-in-JS, Storybook, AWS, Terraform. I am open for relocation.

## **Experience**

Front-end Developer · 08/2016 to 05/2019 Morgan Stanley, Hungary, Budapest

- Architect and develop a widget framework UI
- Improve a data heavy, exception management app which has 10 000 users
- Review code and help junior developers
- Lead retrospective and responsible for team improvement
- Technologies: Angular, TypeScript, JavaScript, SCSS, CSS, REST, Git, Java, Spring, Elasticsearch, SQL

**Software Developer Intern** · 03/2015 to 08/2016 **Morgan Stanley**, Hungary, Budapest

- Create an onboarding and management tool for an internal app
- Improve a to-do application with dev team
- Technologies: AngularJS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, REST, Java, Spring, Elasticsearch, SQL

## **Education**

Master of Science: **Electrical Engineering** · 2010 to 2014 **Budapest University of Technology and Economics**, Hungary, Budapest

Bachelor of Science: **Electrical Engineering**  $\cdot$  2014 to 2016 **Budapest University of Technology and Economics**, Hungary, Budapest